HASAN NASEEM

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

+1 (647) 890 4467 hn92@live.com www.hasannaseem.com https://github.com/hnaseem1

PROFILE

Have you ever tried finding patterns in the most unlikely places like a subway platform? I know I do, to figure out where the train door will open, which always leads me to get off near an exit hence saving time and leading to efficiency. Patterns are beautiful and everywhere and I am always looking out for them, which is why I love clean code. I loved playing around with numbers and I have been making and breaking webpages since I was 12, it is has been my passion, it keeps me curious and makes me intuitively pick up new languages and frameworks

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER

May 2018 - Present

SYSTEMS ANALYST

Raj Products Co. | Aug 2014 - Dec 2017

Worked with the tech team for deployment of a tailor-made RDBMS. Proposed and implemented solutions to automate production processing.

Performed Inventory audits on a weekly basis.

Designed systems workflow

Identify problems and requirements from stakeholders and analyzed data for planning new reports

Highlighting, delegating system bugs and manage tasks and projects through online tools similar to trouble ticket system.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS, MAJOR IN INFORMATION MANAGEMENT, MAJOR IN ACCOUNTING AND FINANCE

University of Sheffield | 2011 - 2014

WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE

Bitmaker Labs | Mar 2018 - May 2018

PROJECTS

OPEN EDX DEVELOPMENT AND DEPLOYMENT

DemocracyKit.org | Jan 2018 - Present

MY TECH STACK



Ruby on Rails





HTML5 & CSS3



Ruby



jQuery



Javascript



PostgreSQL



React.js



Python

LEARNING

React.js Django Component Testing Node.js / Express.js PHP

DevOps Developer Certification